Hey everyone, and thanks for jumping
back into the cryptoverse. This is NFA
Live coming to you on a more bullish day
than we've seen in quite a while.
Bitcoin's back up to about $72,000. So,
we want to go through several different
questions to Guy and Rob. If you're not
subscribed to Guy and Rob, make sure you
do that. Links to their channels are in
the description below. Uh, but first,
let's just check in. How's it How's it
going, Guy?
I'm well, thanks, Ben. I'm well. How are
you?
>> Doing pretty well. Um, how about you,
Rob?
>> I'm doing pretty good. I like these
green days. Everybody seems to be
happier, even though, you know, we're
still down a little bit, but I'll take
these days. These are good days.
>> Hopefully, it's a sign of more green
days next year and and maybe later this
year. I mean, hopefully it's a sign that
things are starting to move in the in a
in a more positive direction. What I
want to do though first is is you know
talk about just that Bitcoin is now
above 70K. Uh you know when I when I was
thinking about asking this question I
was thinking all right it's rallied to
70K what next? Well now it's 72K. So I
mean a lot has happened uh since I went
to sleep last night. Um so what are your
thoughts on that? Uh Rob, why don't I
start with you on this one. Um what are
your thoughts about 70K 72K Bitcoin? you
know, it's August of 2026.
Is this is the is the bare market over?
Um what do you think?
>> Uh I sure hope so, but uh we'll see
where we go from here. And again, like I
mean we've we've heard a lot of
different times where they say the bare
market is over just to kind of fall down
even further. So if you just throw up
the screen real quick. Uh I mean we've
got Ben was right. 72K looking, you
know, pretty good. It's interesting
though over the last seven days just how
things have been pretty much flat and a
little pump right there. S&P 500 is down
just a little bit over the last five
days. So maybe there is this magical
rotation of capital. I know people
sometime people laugh at that. Some
people say it's it's the it's going to
happen. But whatever it is, these are
our prices. And I will tell you it's
pretty interesting that we just had a
massive liquidation event as far as
shorts go over the last year. 2.6
billion shorts liquidated in just one
day. and that I my heart goes out to the
traders out there, but you had it
coming. And with these shorts happening,
uh, this of course buoied the price and
I don't know what's going to happen,
especially if we're talking about, you
know, Iran and America. I mean, we can't
escape geopolitics. Donald J. Trump just
uh announced that they're going to do a
crushing economic operation. We'll see
if this is just another blowhard type of
thing or actually comes to fruition. But
I just tell you like that I'm glad I was
was dollar cost averaging below the
200week moving average and actually a
little bit above it. We can see that you
know over time we've been down below the
200E moving average but look at that
spike. Uh pretty nice, pretty beautiful.
But like I said before, I think it's not
a bad time to accumulate because who
knows if the four years cycle play out
like they've been doing so perfectly,
you know, we could see it go down uh
even further. But right now is a pretty
good day. So, if you're in a little bit
of profit and you want to take some off
the table, that's not a bad idea. That's
what I did this morning. And we can see
that, you know, in 2022, we went below
the 20 week moving average many a time,
even the 250, even the 300week moving
average. But then, as a reminder, in
2018, we never did. And that was another
midterm year, I believe. So, going from
here, it seems like it's the same thing.
It's like we just drop and drop. We chop
sideways, and then then we go down. If
this does actually happen and we
actually get out of this uh this this
market into the bullishness, it'll be
great. And uh I you know hopefully
people have uh purchased a little bit
along the way. But if we just look at
last cycles, it's pretty much matching
up except for this last piece. And this
is where the rubber meets the road. Are
you going to buy? Are you going to wait
for it to go down below that magical
200, 250, 300 moving average and just
kind of wait? Or are you actually going
to get in there? It's it's up to
everybody who is watching, but me
personally, I didn't want to be in that
position. That's why I dollar cost
average every day, every Monday. That's
what I think.
>> Yeah. I mean, I think that makes sense.
And normally, I think we've talked about
before, normally buying Bitcoin in the
second half midterm years tends to work
out pretty well, especially if you can
have like a one to twoyear time horizon
on that. So, hopefully this time is not
different and and it and it ends up
working out. Guy, what do you think? I
mean, are we you think we're back in
business here? Um, is it is it
premature? Where are you on it?
>> Well, I' I'd be cautious about saying
we're back in business. What I would
say, I think, is that it's probably safe
to say we have bottomed now. Um, I would
be I would be very surprised if we if we
went much much lower from here. So, it
looks like the bottom is in and this
could be, you know, the sort of first
leg up of a of a much more of a much
more drawn out rally. Um, I think what's
interesting about or or what's really
important to note about the the rally
that we've seen over the past sort of 24
hours or so is that it's been driven by
short liquidations. you know, we had
this announcement from the Treasury
which kind of kicked everything off, but
um the the the big catalyst was shorts
getting blown out and a lot of people
saw the initial pump uh went short on
that and also got blown out and you know
we've seen this work in the other
direction many many times and now it's
working in in everyone's favor or you
know certainly anyone who's long favor.
Um, so I think what we need to see if
this is going to be if this is going to
be sustained, if this isn't a sort of
fake out, what we need to see is spot
buying because eventually a short
squeeze will will run out of steam. The
shorts will all get blown out and people
and then we'll chop sideways whilst
people sort of reallocate and and
rethink their positions. So we need to
see more spot buying, increased spot
buying if that's going to be a thing.
Can you share my screen there that we've
got the I mean on the spot buying thing,
it's certainly positive uh that the ETF
flows have really picked up. I mean over
half a billion dollars collectively into
Bitcoin ETFs yesterday. That is very
very encouraging. That's what we need to
see. But I think we're going to need to
see more days, more big days of ETF
inflows before we can get really excited
about this possibly having legs uh you
know going into going into the the the
last quarter of the year. So I think I
think the bottom's in. I think things
are looking good. What my my best guess
is that probably um we will retrace a
bit eventually you know in the next few
days perhaps and that 65 to 67k level
which was resistance for so long you
know we've just been sort of chopping
below that and occasionally uh
challenging it and getting rejected that
I think could well flip into support now
and you know give us a bit of support
for the next leg up but My best guess is
that probably we eventually give back
these gains before too long, but it's
certainly a step in the right direction
and yeah, I would say the bottom is
likely in now.
>> Well, there you have it. Um, it look
seems like you guys are are leaning more
in the bullish direction right now,
which is I mean it's certainly nice to
see Bitcoin do something different than
it's been doing for the last several
months. Um I think we volatility was
being compressed to basically levels
that it hardly ever sees, right? So
normally when we get to those levels, we
do see volatility in at least one
direction. Um the next question I have
is, you know, we used to talk about this
more. We don't really talk about it
nearly as much. Uh but the ETH Bitcoin
valuation, so the ETH Bitcoin valuation
is at around 0.03182.
Um and I think around 00312 um but uh
the ETH Bitcoin valuation has actually
been showing a little bit of strength
over the last few weeks. I I think ever
really ever since June or so. Um so what
are your thoughts about Ethereum in this
case because you know ETH going up on
its Bitcoin pair
is is something that we haven't really
seen a lot you know in the last like
four or five years. So, do you guys
think that ETH has turned the corner
against Bitcoin? Uh, I'm curious to to
get your thoughts on that, guy. I'll
start with you on this one.
>> Okay. Yeah, you're right. Um, ETH ETH
BTC has been showing um strength, signs
of strength in recent weeks. The uh ETF
flows for E um for Ethereum ETFs have
been largely positive. Okay, you know,
we're talking nothing like the numbers
for Bitcoin, but um the there is a sense
that institutional flows are moving
towards Ethereum and we did a video on
this recently and a lot of that is just
to do with staking and with yield, you
know, in um institutions especially uh
want to want to earn passive income and
ETH is the ETH is the big uh the the
high market cap crypto that offers that.
Uh meanwhile um exchange balances of ETH
are declining as well. Um sentiment is
improving around Ethereum itself.
Obviously Ethereum is in this constant
state of flux and change. There's a new
um there's a new upgrade a new hard fork
I think coming soon. I think that's
Hegota. I think that's Yeah, I think
it's that one. Um so sentiment
definitely seems to have improved. I
would remind you though that I think
last time I checked ETHBTC was still
down 12.8% 8% year to date. So although
>> we take what we get, guy, [laughter]
>> let's not be let's not be too negative
negative. But yeah, it's definitely it's
definitely showing signs of improving
and obviously that bodess well not only
for ETH but for the wider altcoin
complex as well if certainly if we if we
look at it in terms of if past cycles
but yeah the the certainly the the
sentiment seems to be improving and I
think that's a really important thing to
note as well.
>> Rob Rob, what do you think about ETH? I
mean it's kind of been down and out for
a number of years. I just noticed it
because I've seen it I've seen ETH below
or the the ETH Bitcoin ratio below 0.03
for a while, but on this recent rally by
Bitcoin, ETH what's really interesting
if you kind of look at the nuances of it
is that ETH is going up against Bitcoin,
but also
right now, right? Like the rest of the
altcoin market is going down. So like
what do you make of all this? Is
Ethereum showing showing strength in in
sort of riskier parts of the of the
market than Bitcoin? What do you think?
>> Well, I mean, Guy said it perfectly
about what's going on and the and the
inflows with the ETF, and he's also
correct about uh the, you know, Ethereum
being down against Bitcoin. I think he's
at 12.8% somewhere around there
year-over-year. So, right now, if you
everything just comes down to what is a
distressed asset? Is this is this one of
those? Is this will actually improve?
And it looks like it's actually
happening. I will say that it's pretty
amazing that Tom Lee from Bitmine uh
kept with his thesis and kept buying and
buying. I wonder where we would be with
Ethereum if it wasn't for Tom and Bit
mine buying up all that Ethereum. But it
seems like that it's it's almost like in
the 80s when PCs became prevalent and
you have businesses buy those and then
of course they would put Microsoft on
because no one got fired putting
Microsoft on even though it was kind of
expensive and a little bit clunky. It
didn't really work as well. It's the
same thing with Ethereum. I think that's
what Wall Street is kind of choosing and
some of the institutions are like, well,
you know, I don't want to get fired.
Let's just go with this one. This is the
future of finance and we're going to
defy this way. So, I look at it like one
of those. Um, but as far as like what
you said, Ben, altcoins, you're right.
First of all, most of them should go
away because they're worthless. I think
the ones that actually have utility and
kind of holding up, especially for
stable coins in the rails, I always talk
about the best Binance, Ethereum,
Salana, Tron. If you have those four and
then you know little hyperlquid maybe
canton round it all out things will do
pretty well for altcoins but it's I
think the days of everything going up
are gone and uh it would be probably
behoove a lot of people just to get into
more safer things like Bitcoin Ethereum.
>> Yeah, fair enough. Sorry I didn't I
didn't share your screen. I didn't know
if you wanted me to. You want
>> Oh, it's just your website. Everybody's
seen it.
>> Yeah, you're right. Uh all right. Um
so uh so I mean so one of the kind of an
interesting thing that happened
yesterday is that US Treasury Secretary
uh Scott Bessen he announced that the
Treasury Department would at least
double the size of liquidity support
buyback operations for long-term debt uh
by the government. And I mean I guess
the purpose here is to try to suppress
long the long end of the yield curve.
Try to keep the 30-year down. and try to
keep the 10 year down. That seems like
what they're trying to do. I'm curious,
do you think they will be successful in
that? I mean, do you think that what
they're planning here is is going to be
successful in, you know, keeping the
long end down? I mean, today the long
end's right back up. Uh, but it's hard
to know if that's just like a a dead cat
bounce before it then continues to to go
back down. So, what are your what are
your thoughts on that? And I don't I
mean, do either of you want to take this
one? Not really sure if you know how uh
I mean Guy, do you have any thoughts on
on this particular one?
>> Yeah, sure. I mean, yeah. So, this was
the thing. This was the announcement,
wasn't it, that kind of set everything
off yesterday. And then crypto got the
extra boost from uh from this conference
at the White House and whatever, but
this was the big sort of economic news.
And I mean, this isn't this isn't QE.
This isn't yield curve control. you know
they are still they are they're not
printing money and they are they are
still borrowing you know that that that
is that that hasn't changed and I think
you know is it was it yesterday or the
day before that I think the national
debt the US national debt crossed $40
trillion
um so you know it it it I think really
the more important thing is is the
signal that it sends to the market the
administration is basically saying We
will intervene and do what we can to
keep uh the bond market quiet, to keep
yields under control, to uh you know to
stocks going up, to keep volatility
under control, etc., etc. Um the the
problem is I guess you know that that
sends a good message to the market that
says we will do what we can to to to
keep things under control. The flip side
of the coin is the the the the efficacy
if you like of intervention is pretty
questionable. Look what they did with
the yen recently. Um we had this
unprecedented or or almost unprecedented
joint intervention on the yen from um
from Japan and the US and it didn't
really do all that much. It sort of
stabilized it for a bit and then the yen
started creeping up against the dollar
once again and and that problem has not
gone away. And I think this is kind of
the same thing really. These macro
forces are arguably stronger than what
any one player can do. Even if that is
the biggest player in town, you know,
the United States. Um that said, you
know, markets have got a lift off it
because uh they see that the that the
administration is is is intervening and
that's enough for them. But it doesn't
change the fact that there's a$40
trillion, you know, wall of debt that is
that is growing by the day. And I guess
maybe you could say, you know, maybe
that's one of the reasons Bitcoin has
performed so well because this is
serving to remind everyone of this this
complete debt shitow that is going on.
Not just in the US, you know, Japan, um,
France, the UK, so many of these
countries are just drowning in debt. Um,
but yeah, I I think it's more about a
signal of intent and the market has
enjoyed it so far. Maybe it can keep
going. And of what I guess what's what's
also quite interesting is that this
program this uh you know um these bond
buybacks that the buying back of these
sort of longer older less liquid bonds
goes on from early September to the 4th
of November which I think is the day
after the midterms. I don't know if
there's any coincidence in that at all
but I thought it was I thought it was
interesting. But yeah there we are.
I mean, I I I do think the mantra for
politicians should just be what's a few
trillion dollars among friends, right? I
mean, this is a [clears throat] I mean,
$40 trillion is nice, but it does make
me wonder what 50 trillion is going to
feel like. And and and really they they
probably shouldn't call it the debt
ceiling. It should be more like the debt
target because I mean, every time they
have the ceiling, they just raise the
ceiling when we get to it. And we always
reach it, right? I mean, we always go to
it. Rob, did you want to add anything to
it or
>> No, we should Well, we should call the
the debt suggestion because that's
pretty much what that's that's pretty
much what it is. Hey, I I will say guy
uh your your compatriate Nick had a good
post on X this morning. He says
America's America's debt problem now has
three exits. Cut spending, let yields
run or let the dollar weaken. And it
looks like he says Washington just
picked door three because I think it's
like two to four billion dollars or
something like that that they're they're
injecting in the market. But as a
reminder, I think this is is correct.
Reck me in the comment section. Treasury
statistics, I mean outstanding or
issuance up 10% 18 trillion and
outstanding as of July is $31.5
trillion. So 2 to four billion. I I
think it's posturing. I think Guy maybe
have gotten a pretty good point there
about the midterm elections and
President Trump and then Republicans
saying, "Hey, this is the fiscal
responsibility we're going to pump in
there. We've got your back. But don't
worry because we're going to just start
spending and printing the M2 money
supply. And I think the thesis is good
for us. Everybody here who holds
Bitcoin. If you keep printing, that's
fine because we have hard assets and
we'll take those to the bank. Actually,
not to the bank. But
>> anywhere but the bank.
>> Anywhere but the bank.
>> They won't cash it in, right?
>> They won't cash that check.
>> They might look at you a little crazy.
Um, [clears throat] what are your
thoughts about gold? because I mean, you
know, Bitcoin's been moving up uh
recently, but but gold has also been
moving up, too. And I I'm curious, you
know, is do you think gold is rallying
right now for the same reason that
Bitcoin is, or do you think that it's a
different reason? Like, what do you
think's going on with gold? Uh, Rob,
Guy, either of you? Well, I I mean I
I'll just say that I mean gold it's it's
not just you know retail ETF flows
investors. It's a whole plethora of
different reasons and one of those big
things is central banks. This goes to
2024. We can see how much was purchased
there. But it's also that in Q2
uh the World Gold Council stated that
central banks added 289 tons. That's 62%
62% jump year-over-year and the
strongest quarter. And to put that in
perspective, the entire ETF inflows for
2023 doesn't match what that actually
is, that dollar amount. So, yeah, gold
is a great hedge against inflation. I
think we all know that. But on top of
that, uh we also have that that
beautiful response by the central banks
to go, we'll just buy gold. And that's a
big thing. I think if we can remember
remember the promise in 2017, we can get
a if we get a Bitcoin ETF and the
government behind us, it's just too
valhalla and we're going to keep going.
Well, we hit that in 2025. I think the
only the next big thing is more
institutions, more sovereign nations and
central banks putting that on the
balance sheet. We get that then of
course we go we go pretty uh
up and to the right. But as far as like
gold, I think it's doing what it's
always done, sniff out little hedge
against inflation and central banks buy
it like crazy,
>> right? So maybe slightly different
reason I guess for gold up than than
Bitcoin then. More of a Yeah,
>> more more of a Yeah, more of a hedge.
And of course, like Guy talked about, we
are we have the benefit of all those
shorts being liquidated and a little
pump right here. But August is known for
a little bit of pump, but then
September, October, we'll see.
>> Well, they were talking about I mean,
wasn't Trump just talking about crypto
yesterday or Bitcoin in general or the
last couple of days or so? And I mean, I
can't help but feel like it's more of a
like a, hey, the midterms are coming up.
let's pretend like we care about crypto
again type thing because I I don't feel
like I mean ever since the meme coins
launched I'm not really sure what really
happened but um anyways I I digress I
digress
there was a um
>> there was a conference at the White
House yesterday I think a lot of crypto
a lot you know um your Brian Armstrongs
and Brad Garlingous and whatever and I
think yeah he Trump was there and I
think he mentioned hyperlquid
>> um And so that that got a sort of name
check. Hence hence why hype's done so
well. But actually also, you know, he
did sort of say, come on, let's get the
clarity act done. Let's get this let's
get this over the line, which I think is
also a reason that you can give for
crypto sort of outperforming everything
else at the moment. It kind of got a
triple whammy. You know, it got this
macro announcement that kind of listed
um this bond announcement that lifted
everything. Then it got um this this big
meeting at at the White House and Trump
sort of showing an interest again. I
mean, you know, probably Baron holds a
load of hype, so you know, he just
decided to pump that. But then also, you
know, the CF the CFTC and the SEC are,
you know, making noises about the
regulations that they've drawn up for
crypto as well. And now the Clarity Act
has got a little bit more of a of a shot
in the arm. So, you know, it's kind of a
it's not I wouldn't I'd hesitate to call
it a perfect storm, but it's crypto has
certainly got like a sort of triple
boost if you like over the past 24
hours. And as far as gold's concerned, I
mean, I think it's I think it is similar
in a way. I think I think gold is
sniffing out that that $40 trillion in
in US national debt as well. As Rob
said, central banks are hoarding it on a
on a massive scale. And if you look at
the uh geopolitical risk premium, I mean
that just that just doesn't doesn't seem
to be slowing down, does it? I I read I
wish I could um find a link to it
because it was really interesting, but I
read a very good article just yesterday,
I think, that saying the Iranian regime
now has much more of an incentive to
keep this thing going than it does to
end it. Because if if it allows the war
to end and comes to an agreement that
opens the straight again, yada yada
yada, then they've got to confront the
absolutely diabolical situation at home,
you know, rampant inflation, an economy
that's in the toilet, etc., etc.
Whereas, if they can keep the war going
with the United States, they've got, you
know, they've got something that to
focus the population on, uh, you know, a
perpetual state of war actually works
for them. So any idea that this whole
situation might come to an end and that
horm traffic might get back to normal
and inflation might go back down because
the oil I don't think that's going to
happen personally that that is looking
less and less likely because one side
just does not have any incentive to
finish it. So in that situation again I
think that makes the case for gold quite
strongly.
>> It all points to assets. Well said.
Well, I mean, I think that's I mean,
it's always all pointed to assets,
right? Because inflation will uh will
eat you alive if if you're not invested
over over a long period of time. Uh,
last question and and that is everyone's
favorite question is more about monetary
policy.
Rob Rob's been eager.
>> I don't This is a guy question. It's a
guy. We we've already um uh we've
already seen, you know, some central
banks raise rates. So, the Bank of Japan
has been raising rates. Australia
started raising rates, I think, in like
February or March or something. They've
raised rates several times. New Zealand
uh is has raised rates already. The
Europe area, we already saw a rate hike
over there. Is the US next in line? I
mean, there's, you know, there's a lot
of speculation back and forth whether
we're going to get a rate hike or not.
Um, and so I'm I'm curious what you guys
think about that because I mean if you
look at prediction markets or or you
know CME Group, whatever it is, like the
markets seem open-minded to a rate hike
before the end of the year. Are you guys
on the same page, guy? Are you on the
same page as that or you think the uh
the markets are worrying about something
they don't need to worry about?
>> I No, I think I think a rate hike is
still very much on the table. Certainly
it's it's retreated in in recent weeks.
But one thing that kind of got a little
overlooked yesterday in all the
excitement around this uh announcement
from the Treasury was uh the minutes of
the FOMC from last month um which said
if I recall that they they could still
consider hikes and I think overall the
minutes leaned hawkish. Um and then when
you factor in the you know the straight
of horses is still closed and the
inflation picture remains remains pretty
dicey. I think there is definitely still
a a more than decent chance. Maybe not
in September but I think there are
meetings in in November and December.
There are still three more FOMC's to
come this year. Um it will be very
interesting to see what Kevin Walsh will
say at Jackson Hole. I think he speaks
there tomorrow. And actually, [cough]
excuse me, that's something I should
have pointed out earlier for the first
question as well. One thing that could
derail this whole hike if is if Kevin
Walsh comes out tomorrow is really
hawkish. Um this whole this whole rally
that we I I mean to say, you know, he
could come out and Kevin Walsh is is not
afraid to sort of do things his way.
He's cut this forward guidance uh
business. So, you know, there's a lot
more uncertainty around that. There is a
chance he could come out at Jackson Hole
tomorrow and just be really negative and
spook the markets right out. But, um,
yeah, I I I think that hawkish tone from
the minutes and the fact that the
inflation that the things causing
inflation haven't been resolved, I think
that means yeah, we shouldn't rule out a
rate hike at all. Didn't it Trump
yesterday or sometime recently? I I feel
like I heard the problem is I don't even
know what to like when I see these
things on on Twitter, I'm like, is it
real or is it AI? I don't even know
anymore. [laughter]
>> And I I stopped even trying to to figure
it out. But I saw a video of him talking
where he basically said, you know, in
strong in strong markets or strong
economies, you would expect rate hikes
and you would expect rate cuts and weak
economy. It almost feels like he's
trying to prepare people, you know, for
a potential rate hike. But I mean, I
don't know why he was given pals so
much, you know what over this. I mean,
what did we say like a year ago? We're
like, what if what if Trump gets the
person he wants in and then the first
move for that guy is to actually raise
rates rather than a lower rate, which I
mean, right now seems like a more likely
outcome to me. Like, it seems like the
next move is more likely a rate hike
than a rate cut. Not like another rate
hiking cycle, but maybe just another
rate hike, like one rate hike. Um,
>> I don't know, Rob.
>> I I mean,
I mean, the only thing Guy said
everything perfectly, but I mean, Wars
is just gonna have to decide if he's
going to be Vulkar or if he's going to
be Burns. Which one is he going to be?
The one that was remembered for pushing
the uh uh inflation to the moon or is it
a Vulker to bring everything down, but
it was very difficult and then have to
go against Trump and then have to do
that S show. So, I don't know where it's
going to go, but we'll see.
>> All right. Well, we've gone through all
the questions for today. Um, I was
trying to look to see if I saw any any
good questions in the chat. If you guys
have any, we'll leave a question down
below. Maybe we'll try to see one or two
of them. Uh, let's see.
Some people are talking about property
in New Zealand's down 30%. Is I'm going
to New Zealand next month, so maybe I
should should buy some property there.
>> What's another another conference, Ben,
or what are you doing?
>> Uh, yeah, I'm speaking at a at a tech
conference in New Zealand.
>> Oh, nice. Hey, how's the uh how's the
conference in Miami? I think a lot of
people should come to that. Be a nice
little vacation for them.
>> Yeah,
>> you can see NFA Live live.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Maybe maybe that should just be
called NFA Live and this should not be
called live.
>> Yeah. NFA not live.
>> Yeah. Um
>> NFA not quite live. Um mind you, I think
the New Zealand property market was
ridiculous. I remember reading about
that a while ago and quite a lot of New
Zealanders have have left because the
property market was so hot they just
couldn't get couldn't couldn't find
anywhere to live. Um it's happening in
the UK as well. There has been a decline
in property prices there as well.
>> I was talking to uh Jason Pazino uh he's
you know he's in Australia and he said
he said real estate prices you know in
Australia in some of the areas are are
just down a ton right now. Um, right
there.
>> Yeah, there's a lot of like in I I know
in Florida they're having just a massive
influx of of houses and the prices are
going down, but there's always it's it's
like like we say there's a bull run
somewhere. There's some different places
that have actually are up, but not much,
>> right?
>> All right. Um, so I mean I guess that'll
wrap it up for today. Uh, if you guys
are not subscribed to Guy's channel and
Rob's channel, make sure you do that. do
so. Link in the description below. Uh,
next week we will be on Rob's channel.
So, uh, I look forward to seeing you
guys there. And thank you too for for
joining me on uh for the stream this
week.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Cheers, guys.